(ringing)
(Amy:)Oh, uh, ok...
(Amy:)Uh, here's our first call.
(Sheldon:)Hello, and welcome
to Fun With Flags.
(Amy:)What's your question?
KOOTHRAPPALI:
What is wrong with me?
(Raj(voice):)Why am I so self-destructive?
(Amy:)Rajesh?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Raj:)You two look happy...
how do you do it?
I-I think it starts
with good communication.
Yeah, wait, that's not a flag
question. Next caller.
(Howard:)I hope you don't think
I'm just saying this
(Howard:)because it's
Valentine's Day, but...
(Howard:)I love you so much.
(Bernadette:)I'm gonna put this
down your robe.
(Bernadette:)It's not moving,
but I think it's still alive.
(Howard:)Well, should we put it back
in there a few minutes?
(Leonard:)No.
(Bernadette:)No, and it's not a rat,
it's a rabbit.